(Leonard:)Hey, Penny and I are gonna go
shop for a dining room table.
(Leonard:)You want to come with us?
I'd love to, but, I'm too busy
(Sheldon:)falling back in love
with Windows 98.
(Leonard:)Seriously? You haven't used
this desk in years.
(Leonard:)The second I want to get rid of it,
you're up here working?
(Sheldon:)I can't talk right now.
(Sheldon:)I have several thousand updates
to install.
(Leonard:)Are you really
gonna sit here all day?
(Sheldon:)Think of me as Arthur Dent in
(Sheldon:)Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy,
(Sheldon:)lying in front of the bulldozers
to protect his home.
(Leonard:)If you'll recall, the Vogon fleet
blew up the Earth anyway.
It's a made-up story. I don't even
know why you're talking about it.
(Leonard:)I'm putting all this stuff
in storage. We don't need any of it.
(Sheldon:)How can you say that?
(Sheldon:)You show me one thing
in here we can live without.
(Leonard:)Hang on.
(Leonard:)Check your in-box.